BLACK FRIDAY - 20% off everything in the store - 10% off Raspberry Pi boards (see homepage banner for exceptions)BLACK FRIDAY - 20% off everything in the store - 10% off Raspberry Pi boards (see homepage banner for exceptions)

Navigation

   No results found

Currency

GBP

Country/region

GBP USD CAD EUR

Login / Signup

[0

Cart](https://thepihut.com/cart)

    Handy Links

    Categories

    [
    
    #### Raspberry Pi 5
    
    2-3x the CPU performance with loads of great new features!](https://thepihut.com/products/raspberry-pi-5)[
    
    #### Raspberry Pi Pico 2 W
    
    Now with wireless! The Raspberry Pi Pico 2 W.](https://thepihut.com/products/raspberry-pi-pico-2-w)

    Handy Links

    Categories

    [
    
    #### Addressable RGB LEDs
    
    Easy-to-use RGB LEDs to light up your next project, in a range of handy formats!](https://thepihut.com/collections/adafruit-neopixels)[
    
    #### Microcontrollers!
    
    Hundreds of microcontrollers to choose from - we've got something for every project!](https://thepihut.com/collections/adafruit-development-boards)

    Handy Links

    Categories

    [
    
    #### BBC micro:bit V2
    
    The NEW micro:bit V2 - now with a speaker, microphone and touch sensor!](https://thepihut.com/products/micro-bit-v2)[
    
    #### BBC micro:bit V2 GO Starter Kit
    
    Everything you need to start using the micro:bit - includes a micro:bit V2!](https://thepihut.com/products/micro-bit-v2-go-starter-kit)

    Handy Links

    Categories

    [
    
    #### Arduino UNO R4 WiFi
    
    The latest UNO, now with onboard WiFi and a 12x8 LED matrix!](https://thepihut.com/products/arduino-uno-r4-wifi)[
    
    #### Arduino Nano ESP32
    
    The power of the ESP32 with the support of the Arduino ecosystem](https://thepihut.com/products/arduino-nano-esp32-with-headers)

    By Store

    By Price

    [
    
    #### The Pi Hut e-Gift Card
    
    Give them the gift of choice with The Pi Hut e-Gift card!](https://thepihut.com/products/gift-card)[
    
    #### Raspberry Pi Pico Kit!
    
    An affordable gift option with everything they need to get started!](https://thepihut.com/products/starter-kit-for-raspberry-pi-pico-includes-pico-h)

* Raspberry Pi
    
    Raspberry Pi
    
    * The Raspberry Pi
        
        The Raspberry Pi

    * SD Cards & Storage
        
        SD Cards & Storage

    * Power Supplies
        
        Power Supplies

    * HATs, pHATS & GPIO
        
        HATs, pHATS & GPIO

    * Cases
        
        Cases

    * Cooling
        
        Cooling

    * Camera
        
        Camera

    * Screens & Displays
        
        Screens & Displays

    * Cables
        
        Cables

    * USB Add-ons
        
        USB Add-ons

    * Arcade
        
        Arcade

* Maker Store
    
    Maker Store
    
    * Accessories
        
        Accessories

    * Audio
        
        Audio

    * Breakouts & Modules
        
        Breakouts & Modules

    * Cables
        
        Cables

    * Components & Parts
        
        Components & Parts

    * Development Boards
        
        Development Boards

    * Displays
        
        Displays

    * Enclosures & Fixings
        
        Enclosures & Fixings

    * LEDs
        
        LEDs

    * Power
        
        Power

    * Prototyping
        
        Prototyping

    * Robotics
        
        Robotics

    * Sensors
        
        Sensors

    * 3D Printing
        
        3D Printing

* micro:bit
    
    micro:bit

* Arduino
    
    Arduino
    
    * Shields
        
        Shields

* Gifts
    
    Gifts

GBP

Country/region

GBP USD CAD EUR

Login / Signup

 E-mail

 Password [Forgot password?](https://thepihut.com/account/#recover)

Login New customer?[Create an account](https://thepihut.com/account/register)

Huge Range

Five Star Service

No Quibble Returns

Next Day Delivery

Go to slide 1 Go to slide 2 Go to slide 3 Go to slide 4

Cart

Your cart is empty

Privacy Statement
=================

This Privacy Policy describes how your personal information is collected, used, and shared when you visit or make a purchase from thepihut.com (the “Site”).  
  
**PERSONAL INFORMATION WE COLLECT**  
When you visit the Site, we automatically collect certain information about your device, including information about your web browser, IP address, time zone, and some of the cookies that are installed on your device. Additionally, as you browse the Site, we collect information about the individual web pages or products that you view, what websites or search terms referred you to the Site, and information about how you interact with the Site. We refer to this automatically-collected information as “Device Information”.  
  
We collect Device Information using the following technologies:  

* “Cookies” are data files that are placed on your device or computer and often include an anonymous unique identifier. For more information about cookies, and how to disable cookies, visit [http://www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/).
* “Log files” track actions occurring on the Site, and collect data including your IP address, browser type, Internet service provider, referring/exit pages, and date/time stamps.
* “Web beacons”, “tags”, and “pixels” are electronic files used to record information about how you browse the Site.

Additionally when you make a purchase or attempt to make a purchase through the Site, we collect certain information from you, including your name, billing address, shipping address, payment information (including debit/credit card numbers), email address, and phone number. We refer to this information as “Order Information”.  
  
When we talk about “Personal Information” in this Privacy Policy, we are talking both about Device Information and Order Information.  
  
**HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?**  
We use the Order Information that we collect generally to fulfill any orders placed through the Site (including processing your payment information, arranging for shipping, and providing you with invoices, customer support and/or order confirmations). Additionally, we use this Order Information to:  

* Communicate with you;
* Screen our orders for potential risk or fraud; and
* When in line with the preferences you have shared with us, provide you with information or advertising relating to our products or services.

We use the Device Information that we collect to help us screen for potential risk and fraud (in particular, your IP address), and more generally to improve and optimize our Site (for example, by generating analytics about how our customers browse and interact with the Site, and to assess the success of our marketing and advertising campaigns).  
  
**SHARING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION**  
We share your Personal Information with third parties to help us use your Personal Information, as described above.

For example, we use **Shopify** to power our online store - you can read more about how Shopify uses your Personal Information here: [https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy](https://www.shopify.com/legal/privacy).

We also use **Google Analytics** to help us understand how our customers use the Site - you can read more about how Google uses your Personal Information here: [https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/). You can also opt-out of Google Analytics here: [https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout).

We also share some minimal essential data with **Reviews.IO** for the purpose of requesting feedback to help us identify any shortfalls in our service or products (this data is only used for this purpose and is not sold or passed on to any other parties). You can read more about how Reviews.IO uses this data here: [https://www.reviews.co.uk/front/user-privacy-policy](https://www.reviews.co.uk/front/user-privacy-policy). You can also opt-out of receiving any feedback requests by selecting the unsubscribe button in any email requests received, or alternatively contact [gdpr@reviews.co.uk](mailto:gdpr@reviews.co.uk) who can also ensure your data is deleted if required.  
  
Finally, we may also share your Personal Information to comply with applicable laws and regulations, to respond to a subpoena, search warrant or other lawful request for information we receive, or to otherwise protect our rights.

**KLARNA**

In order to be able to offer you Klarna’s payment options, we will pass to Klarna certain aspects of your personal information, such as contact and order details, in order for Klarna to assess whether you qualify for their payment options and to tailor the payment options for you.

General information on Klarna you can find [here](https://www.klarna.com/uk). Your personal data is handled in accordance with applicable data protection law and in accordance with the information in [Klarna’s privacy policy](http://cdn.klarna.com/1.0/shared/content/legal/terms/Klarna/en_gb/privacy).

**BEHAVIOURAL ADVERTISING**  
As described above, we use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work.  
  
You can opt out of targeted advertising by using the links below:

* Facebook: [https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads](https://www.facebook.com/settings/?tab=ads)
* Google: [https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous](https://www.google.com/settings/ads/anonymous)
* Bing: [https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads](https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads)
* MailChimp - Using the "UNSUBSCRIBE" link provided at the bottom of every e-mail

Additionally, you can opt out of some of these services by visiting the Digital Advertising Alliance’s opt-out portal at: [http://optout.aboutads.info/](http://optout.aboutads.info/).  
  
**DO NOT TRACK**  
Please note that we do not alter our Site’s data collection and use practices when we see a Do Not Track signal from your browser.  
  
**YOUR RIGHTS**  
If you are a European resident, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted. If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.  
  
Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfil contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above. Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.  
  
**DATA RETENTION**  
When you place an order through the Site, we will maintain your Order Information for our records unless and until you ask us to delete this information.  
  
**MINORS**  
The Site is not intended for individuals under the age of 16  
  
**CHANGES**  
We may update this privacy policy from time to time in order to reflect, for example, changes to our practices or for other operational, legal or regulatory reasons.  
  
**CONTACT US**  
For more information about our privacy practices, if you have questions, or if you would like to make a complaint, please contact us by e-mail at privacy@thepihut.com or by mail using the details provided below:  
  
Mann Enterprises LTD, FAO Privacy Compliance Officer, Homefield Road (West), Haverhill, CB9 8QP, United Kingdom

Handy Links

Got any questions?

Terms & Conditions

Our Store Sections

Follow us

We accept

Visa Mastercard Maestro PayPal Amazon Klarna

© The Pi Hut 2024
